[Music]
fwd introduces three different made
insurance independent add-on coverages
that you can now buy even if your
current made insurance is from another
insurer
add-on one coverage for six monthly
medical examination
medical examinations for your helper are
mandatory
enjoy convenience of conducting these
tests at selected clinics
add on to coverage for performance bond
for philippine embassy if you have a
filipino helper you would be familiar
with the mandatory performance bond that
is required when your helper is going on
home leave or renewing her passport
fwd pays the embassy directly if the
bond is called no additional payment is
required protecting you from unwanted
payment surprises
add on three coverage for cashless
outpatient medical expenses
our simple and convenient add-on covers
your helpers outpatient medical costs
from consultation prescription to
diagnostic tests it is also easy to
customize your coverage to match your
helpers employment period between 6 and
26 months
this gives you peace of mind and have
less financial worry if your helper
falls sick plus enjoy cashless claims
with our ecard with no waiting period
for payouts simply buy our add-on
coverage directly online just one of the
ways we strive to change the way people
feel about insurance get a quote in just
10 seconds
[Music]